Yosef Heifetz

 $0533832023 \cdot yossi.heifetz 06@gmail.com \cdot chafetzy@yatmal.co.il$ 10 אהרון בראנד, Jerusalem, Israel

COMPUTER SCIENCE STUDENT

I will be finishing my B.A. in less than a year. I went to college during my high school years, from which I graduated with excellent grades. I am highly motivated, and I love learning new things on my own or anywhere. I have worked in many different jobs before and have acquired many skills from them.

KEY COMPETENCIES

Code development Website development Graphic design

Database managment (such as Excel) Strong interpersonal skills Excellent communication skills Project develompent

Proactive and self-motivated Exceptional organisational skills

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

United Hatzala Jul 2024 - Present

Logistics & database managment

Managed an equipment warehouse, excel sheets. In my position there I also helped with the renovations.

May 2024 - Aug 2024 **Burgers Bar**

Meal Prep. & kitchen worker

Prepared and served a variety of meals with precision and creativity, consistently meeting or exceeding quality standards and receiving compliments for efficiency and presentation.

Waiter July 2021 - Jan 2024

I worked for two years as a waiter in several working places, and gaind many skills from them.

EDUCATION & CERTIFICATIONS

High school diploma

Majors: Pysics, electronics, math & english

EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

Ariel, Youth movment

I was a counsler 2 years, now as a seiner counsler I am active in the community.

Machanayim, Summer camp